-The first baby didn't make it.
-No, you're -- you're right.
Y-Your sister didn't make it.
-How come?
-Well...
Your mom, she had
some complications.
How do you know
about this stuff, anyway?
-Uncle Mike told me.
- Uncle Mike.
-Yeah, well, listen,
y-your mom's gonna be fine,
and the baby's gonna
be fine this time.
Did you ever tell your mom
you know about this stuff?
-No.
-Oh, so maybe
it's our little secret.
That okay with you?
-You shouldn't keep secrets,
though.
I know, but every now and then,
it's okay to have a secret.
Like the fact
that I let you sit up front.
- Oh, yeah.
-And yeah, sometimes we're gonna
get some candy on the weekdays.
That's a good secret, too.
-Oh, yup. I love that secret.
-Yeah.
-Chocolate.
-Chocolate secrets
are good secrets.
-Yeah.
-It's gonna be okay.
Promise.
You gonna be a good boy?
-You better hurry.
She's waiting for you.
-Yeah. I know.
-Hey, man, uh...
-Yo.
-Did you get my e-mail
about the new schedule?
Because nobody replied.
-Yep. Yeah.
No, everything's okay here,
man. Go be with your wife.
-Yeah, but Rich
left me a message.
I was wondering...
-Let it go. Let it go.
I don't want to talk to you
till Monday,
and I'll handle fucking Rich.
-Alright. Thanks.
-You excited?
Excited?
-Okay. Alright. Alright.
-I'll talk to you later.
Good luck.
-Alright. Later.
-Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is it a boy or girl?
You never said.
-We don't know.
It's a --
You know, she wanted it
to be -- or, you know,
we wanted it to be a surprise.
-Well, I hope
it looks more like her.
Jeez, I hope it looks more
like her.
Yeah, me too.
-Hey.
-Hey. Did you drop him
at my mother's?
-Yeah. Yeah, he's fine.
Uh, so, do you need anything
from --
-Oh, hold on.
The doctors just walked in.
-Hello, Mrs. Chamberlain.
Alright, just relax your back.
-Mrs. Chamberlain.
-Put this behind you there.
-Right there.
-Oh!
-Good. Good.
-Good job.
Just move -- rest this foot.
- You want your legs bent,
to look like this.
Right, exactly.
-You okay?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
I keep thinking it's not
supposed to hurt this much.
-You don't remember
it hurting this much?
-Oh. Oh.
Oh!
-I'm gonna grab the hand.
-Hold on, hold on.
-Can you see where we are?
-I had complications
the first time.
Did they tell you that?
-Yep, I saw it in your chart.
-Okay, just keep breathing.
-Just breathe.
Breathe, baby.
-You want to brace yourself?
- Just like that?
-That's not the board.
-David, are you still there?
-Yeah, I-I-I'm still here.
I'm almost there, babe.
Okay? I'm almost there.
-Okay. I love you.
-I love you, too.
-Come on.
-You leaving?
-Yeah, I'm packing.
-What the fuck?
S-Sir, what --
what are you doing?
-Just...
Pick a card.
-Buddy, I-I'm not an Uber,
okay?
A-A-Are you robbing me?
-I didn't say I was robbing you.
I said pick a card.
Come on. A card.
A card. You know.
Clubs.
Hearts.
-You want me to s-say a card?
-Yes!
-Ace.
-Oh, ace.
And the suit?
-Spades.
I just knew you were
gonna say that card.
Drive.
-S-sir, my wife
is in the hospital.
She's about to give birth.
- Drive.
Exit the hospital and then
go right towards the strip.
Because I...
-Sir.
-...I like the lights.
I-I-I have an emergency.
Okay?
This is a family emergency.
-I'm your family emergency now.
Drive.
-Drive where?
- Jesus Christ.
Drive!
-Where do you want me to go?
-What the fuck
are you looking at?
-Hey, I-I really need
to get back to the hospital --
-Turn here. Here.
-Listen, I just want to say that
whatever it is that you want,
it's yours. I-I mean it.
Just want you to understand --
-Now you're gonna talk
about your family.
-What?
-You're gonna dive into
the bit about your family,
about how much you love them.
with all your heart
and all your goddamn soul.
-Yeah, I was.
-Well, isn't that
a bit of a cliché?
-You want me to take it?
Before the interruption,
you were about to start up
with your phony family speech.
About how if I were to shoot you
through your stupid little
earlobe right now,
the bullet would,
metaphorically speaking,
tear through your wife
and son as well.
-Where are we going?
What do you want?
-Take this next exit.
Pull over.
Still got a few miles
to go before we sleep.
Great night.
Great fucking night.
You're gonna have
to watch the speeding
when you get back up
on the highway.
The adrenaline.
You know, back in South Boston,
I once got three
speeding tickets in one month.
Want to know why?
Stress.
Fuck.
$2,000 boots.
You just watch the speed limit,
obey the traffic signals...
we'll be alright.
Sup?
Well, hi.
I don't blame you.
Might be your one and only shot.
But maybe I was following you.
Maybe I know where you live.
So you run for it.
Now you've involved
your family, too.
-Just relax, okay?
I'm getting in the car.
-It's kind of impersonal,
talking to the back
of your fucking skull.
-You made
a wise decision back there.
-Moving very slowly
into your glove compartment.
-About two months?
-Oh-ho!
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho.
Can somebody say sexy?
-Can you look at the road,
please, when you're driving?
Where are you from, anyways?
-Tucson.
-Have you ever been to Boston?
-Yeah. I've been there once.
Years ago.
-Not for nothing,
but you remind me
of this guy I used to know
in Boston.
And this guy used to drink a
bottle of Glenlivet every night.
Just kill the whole thing
right before bed.
-Well, I don't drink.
-Anymore?
-I haven't had a drink
in years.
- Phony. It's phony.
And that one time
you were in Boston,
was it business or pleasure?
-It was business.
And what business are you in?
-I work for a shipping company.
Mostly warehouse work.
-And you're sure that's the only
time you've been to Boston?
-Yeah.
-You stopped drinking...when?
15 years ago?
I don't remember, but...
Yeah, something like that.
-See, that's funny.
You making an error like that
this early in the evening?
That's really not like you.
-What?
-Is it okay if I ask a question?
-Why wouldn't it be okay?
-How long is this gonna take?
When will I be back home?
-Why would you assume
you'll ever go home again?
-What?
-Did you not just hear me?
-Yeah, I...
-Alright. This whole trip
won't take more than an hour.
We're going to Boulder City.
-Okay.
I can do that.
-Oh, thank you.
Well, that's very
thoughtful of you.
My mother,
she's dying of cancer --
the lung variety.
She's a devout Catholic,
so we gotta do last rites --
-Your mother's at the hospital?
-Don't interrupt me.
That's rude,
you interrupting me.
Don't.
-My mom was also religious.
It didn't stop her
from marrying my dad,
who liked to get drunk and beat
the living shit out of her.
-Just my opinion --
that plea for sympathy
is very beneath you.
So anyway, back to my story.
You take me to the hospital,
the Boulder City Hospital --
Don't you have a car?
Fucking prick.
-W-What is this, "SD love?"
W-What are you, a teenager?
-My son did that.
It's our initials,
me and my wife.
-Oh, isn't that sweet?
You want me to take it, "D?"
-Yeah.
-David, where are you?
It's happening now.
-I'm sorry, babe. I-I'm trying.
I'm almost there.
- Great. Now the little...
-You said you were here!
Why are you late with this?
You're never late.
-I love you so much, baby.
-Doctor, it's normal.
-I'm almost there.
Oh, you said you'll be here!
-I will.
I'm doing everything I can.
- Something's wrong.
It's wrong.
-What is that?
Who's with you?
-Nobody, honey, it's...
the window open.
-Okay.
-Mrs. Chamberlain,
I need you
to put the phone down.
-Doctor, why is it
taking so long?
When we lost our first,
it also took so long.
-Mom, look at me.
-Tell him, honey.
David, tell him what happened.
-Where the fuck are we going?!
-For the devil may start
to envy those
who suffer too deeply
and throw them out
into Heaven.
-So when we get
to the Boulder City,
I drop you off, right?
I drop you off, and...
you let me go.
-I let you go.
-Okay.
-Well, now you've fucking
gone and done it.
Gonna stop?
Would you calm down?
-I'm stopping?
I'm stopping?
-Turn here.
-As I said, all I need is for
you to take me to my mother,
so there's no reason
for anything horrible
to befall anyone tonight.
But if you so much as look
at this cop weird,
I will shoot you so fast in
the back of your goddamn skull,
cranial matter will splatter all
over this cop's pressed uniform,
and it will be disgusting.
-Not a good time.
-License and registration,
please.
-Right. One second.
-M-May I ask
why we're we being pulled over?
-Sure, you can ask.
License and registration.
-Asking permission
to ask the question.
Isn't that the same
as asking the question?
-You were going
11 over the speed limit.
-Well, wait, w-what about the,
uh --
what do you call it?
The flow, right?
The flow of traffic?
-License and registration.
I'm not asking again.
-Well, if all the other cars
are going ten miles over,
you got to do the same, right?
To ensure you don't cause
a traffic hazard.
-One second. U-Uh, my license --
-Just shush.
I'm just asking a question.
What's wrong with that?
-Sir, one more question, and
you're gonna have some trouble.
Oh, no, not trouble.
Please, Mr. Big Policeman,
anything but trouble.
-No, no, w-wait, wait.
-It's okay. I just --
-But isn't that a thing,
though?
The flow.
Isn't that a real thing?
-Sir. Step out of the car.
Out of the car.
-Out of the car.
Are you fucking crazy?
All I did was ask
a simple question,
and now this big cock cop
is telling me
to get out of the car.
-You're under arrest.
Sir,
step out of the vehicle now.
-Just do what he says, okay?
-No!
No, he's too rude.
He's way too fucking rude.
-Now, out!
-I'm not gonna reward
that type of behavior.
-Out of the vehicle now!
-Or what? Really?!
You're gonna shoot me, man?
For not getting out of the car,
you're gonna shoot me
in front of my friend here?
-We're not friends.
-Out of the fucking car.
- Because this Officer Cock.
-Control 1-Nora-61.
-Get behind me, Satan.
-What?
-Uh...
I told you not to speed.
I even warned you once --
no, twice.
I warned you about the speed,
and you wouldn't listen.
-You warned me.
-I told you a couple of times.
-You've warned --
You warned me not to speed.
-Why are you being such a cock
about it?
-Jesus Christ!
-What's past is past,
I always say,
Although others say past
is prologue,
which is really just saying
the same thing
from a different perspective.
But point is, move on here.
Go back to Galleria.
-He was just doing his job.
-He was an authoritarian
little prick.
-He was just a guy doing
his job.
You just killed him.
-Would you just shut up
and drive?
-He could have had a family.
A wife and kids.
-Shut up and drive!
-You could have just destroyed
a whole fucking family!
-I destroyed a family.
I destroyed a family!
I did!
Drive!
-No.
-The next one goes
through your face.
Drive.
-Such bravado all of a sudden.
I wonder, how did that happen?
You going from being such
a whiny little piece of shit
to someone who could
headbutt a horse?
Why?
-Why what?
Why are you doing this?
-I told you.
My mother. The hospital.
Didn't I already tell you this?
-It's bullshit.
-Just tell me.
Just tell me.
-The plain and simple truth,
is that what you want?
-Yeah.
-Although the truth is rarely
plain and never simple.
You remember who said
that one, "D?"
It's too early to spoil
everything.
Me telling you now.
Pull over next exit.
I'm famished.
You got a problem with that?
I can hear you thinking.
-What are you talking about?
-You're working it out.
-I'm just driving.
-No, you're thinking about
crashing into something.
You gotta be real careful.
Blunt trauma to the head.
Man your age.
-I think you broke
my beautiful nose!
Fucker!
[Ringing stops
-Hello.
Oh, hi.
No, no, he's on
the other line right now.
Who, me? Uh...
I work at the gift shop
at the hospital.
Yeah. No, he had to take a call
from the warehouse,
so he's using my land line.
Better reception.
But I am glad you called,
because he wanted me to ask
you what room number you're in.
Okay. Uh-huh.
I'm sorry to hear that.
That does sound painful.
If it's any consolation,
when my wife was pregnant
and delivering,
there was so much pressure
on her bladder --
I mean, it was bitchin'.
It was a golden shower
explosion cascading
all over the doctor's face.
It was sexual, man!
Hey, come on.
Screw you too, lady.
Huh?
You like that?
What do you think?
Still sexy?
I dressed up for this night.
Now you --
you break my nose?!
I-I wanted to be 100% sex
tonight,
and you cut that in half.
I'm now 50% sex. Look.
See that?
I'm Edward G., see?
I'm Edward G. Robinson.
You can't kill me, see?
Yeah.
Come on, sugar.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
Don't fucking do that again.
-Is she okay?
Just tell me she's okay.
-She's fine.
You think she's the first
woman ever to go into labor?
-She had complications
in the past.
Please,
I need to be there.
-Drive!
-Wow! David Chamberlain,
you stud muffin.
I wonder how many blue collar
losers know how to do that?
-Well, she sounded real nice.
I think she was a bit
confused.
Suspicious even, but nice.
-She never told you
the room number?
-She wanted to know why
you weren't at the hospital yet.
She did seem very concerned
about that.
-You don't even know the floor.
-Oh, wow.
A new baby.
Gosh, a brand new baby.
How exciting.
I mean, are you happy?
Objectively speaking,
would you say you and your wife
have a happy marriage?
-Happy?
-Yeah.
-Objectively?
Yeah, we're happy.
Sometimes we feel like we're
the only happy people we know.
Like we got this secret.
-Well, I've never been happy.
You know why?
Sinuses.
-Ever since I was a small child,
I've had a stuffy nose,
and even at the tender age
of two years old,
I knew the cause
of my stuffy nose.
I could see it in my dreams.
And the cause was the Mucus Man.
And the Mucus Man was
a skinny guy in a suit
and tie with a bald head
and a briefcase
full of boogers.
And I -- I could see him
in my mind's eye going up,
up, up in an elevator,
briefcase in hand,
and he glided across the floor,
almost like a like
a snail's trail.
And he got to my bed,
and he opened the briefcase,
and he scooped out
a handful of boogers,
and he sprinkled them
into my nose.
-Roadhouse Diner.
-Go there.
-Clean up.
-Table over here.
Sit down there.
-Faggot.
-Alright, now listen.
There's a certain man --
a very, very important man --
who is waiting
for our arrival.
Well, rather not for us
as much as you.
He's waiting for you.
His associates
were the ones who found you
in the first place.
-They found the wrong guy.
-Now, the initial plan was to
drive you all the way to Boston,
but this old fucking Mickey
was too antsy.
He couldn't wait. He was like
a child on Christmas Eve.
So he flew out tonight
to this private airstrip
in Boulder City,
and that's where we're going.
I hope that answers
some of your questions.
No substitutions.
Can you believe this shit?
Does that look right to you?
Hey, you're not listening to me.
Okay, I'm gonna tell you
a story, and you better listen.
Once upon a time,
many, many years ago,
there was a bookkeeper
from Brooklyn
who was living in South Boston,
and the bookkeeper was working
for a hard-drinking Catholic
named Jacob Sullivan.
-Who's waiting for me?
-Yeah.
-So the bookkeeper
meets a nice Bostonian gal,
falls in love,
gets married, has a baby.
Cute little girl.
Okay, when this waitress asks
you what happened to your face,
I want you to tell her
you fell down the stairs.
-You want me to say --
-"I fell down the stairs."
Say it. Try it out.
"I fell down the stairs."
-I fell down the stairs.
-That's right.
You fell down the stairs,
you stupid, clumsy shit.
-I fell down the stairs.
-He fell down the stairs.
-He fell down the stairs,
but then what happened to you?
-I was at the bottom
of the stairs when he fell.
-Well, good evening, then.
Or is it morning?
I'm never sure what to say
during this witching hour.
-Huh.
Coffee, black.
-And for you?
-What?
-For you?
-Uh, the same.
-Uh, just so you know,
the special today
or tonight --
The special this morning
is open-faced tuna melts.
That's gonna be two pieces
of rye mayonnaise, tuna,
a slice of tomato in each,
and melted mozzarella on top.
-Oh, uh, what happens
if I want cheddar instead?
-Owner's rules.
Who happens to be the cook.
Who happens to be back
in the kitchen right now.
-No shit?
So he is serious about this
"no substitutions" business.
That's a real thing.
-Mm-hm.
But, uh, maybe I'll slice you
a block of cheddar
under the table.
-That's very sweet of you.
-I'll go get those coffees.
-Alright, back to our story.
So what happens is this.
The bookkeeper's 9 to 5 back
then was doing the books
for one of Sullivan's
associates.
But the associate gets
a little too fucking smart
and starts skimming money
on the side.
So when Jacob Sullivan
finds out,
he tells the bookkeeper
to invite the associate over
because two of them
were good friends.
So the bookkeeper's wife
and daughter visit her mother
and the associate comes over.
They have some drinks,
have some cigars,
and once he's good and sloshed,
a few of Sullivan's guys
pay a little visit.
One of them puts a .45
to the back of his skull,
pulls the trigger.
And the same thing
is gonna happen to you when we
get to Boulder City.
Hi. Okay.
Open-faced tuna melt for me.
Swap the mozzarella for cheddar,
if you can slip that past
your goddamn creep of a boss.
-For you?
-Nothing.
-No, order something.
-I'm not hungry.
-I want you to order something.
-What do you mean
you're not hungry?
-I mean, I'm not hungry.
-Then get something
for the road?
-I'm not hungry!
-Order something,
you stupid fuck!
-Tuna melt.
-You want cheddar on that
or mozzarella?
-What?
-Cheddar or mozzarella?
You gotta pick one.
-Cheddar.
-Okay. I've been thinking about
what you've given me so far --
this pathetic and phony
biography of yours,
designed to garner sympathy.
In my experience, most people
tend to think having a family
makes them more sympathetic.
Before anyone takes a bullet
to the head,
they're always prattling on
about their fucking daughter
this,
their fucking son that.
But the fact that you --
you would do that
strikes me
as, um...
tone deaf.
Usually, I wait for the sun to
go down before I start drinking,
but today, I've been
drinking all day.
Ask me why.
I've been drinking all day.
Ask me.
You know, I do think about
the way your life has gone,
how happy you are.
How you've got the secret
fucking happiness.
New wife, new son,
eternal goddamn love.
-Please. Please.
Who do you think I am?
-You're the witching hour.
The waitress,
she mentioned that earlier.
Do you know what that is?
It's European folklore
noting a particular
time of night
when all
the supernatural creatures
slither out and run amok.
-I don't --
-I always liked it.
I liked the idea of crazy --
-I have no idea --
-Do not fucking interrupt me!
God damn it!
I told you that in the car!
You're always running off
at the mouth!
You got a motor mouth!
There's a motor boat
stuck in your mouth!
Just shut up!
Sit the fuck back down!
-I'm watching you.
Okay?
One move, I'm gonna shoot you.
Do you understand?
-Yeah.
Okay.
Give me your cell phones.
Now, if it's not too much
trouble,
I would appreciate
if you would stand behind
the counter where I can see you.
And I don't need to go
into the whole spiel
as to what this gun does to the
face if you try anything smart.
Right? Okay. How much longer
do we have on those tuna melts?
-Um, just a few minutes.
-Okay.
I want them done
in five minutes. Come on.
Actually, no.
Four minutes.
And we want cheddar on them.
You got that? Cheddar.
Nobody puts mozzarella
on a tuna melt.
Luck of the draw.
-Okay.
I have decided that
we should play a little game.
It's called Stop the Phony.
-Let's just go and leave
everyone else out of this.
-I want you to tell me
the truth, the whole truth,
nothing but the truth,
so help you God,
this very minute, right now.
If you don't tell me the truth,
I am gonna kill your
little waitress friend,
I am gonna kill
Mr. Happy Trucker over there,
and anyone else
unfortunate enough
to enter this establishment.
Ready?
Magic Rabbit Foot says go.
Tick, tick, tick, tick.
-The truth?
-Yes, the truth.
The truth, you fucking phony.
The truth.
-The truth is, I-I have no idea
what you're talking about!
-No, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't do this.
This is where the game
gets good!
Don't ruin it.
-Hey, I-I never got your name.
-Oh.
-Let's just get out of here,
just you and me.
-Oh, you sound
kind of cool there.
Oh, my God. So cool.
Almost like you've had
a gun on you before.
Well, let's just make sure
everything's okay.
-Honey. I'm --
-...Car's extended warranty.
Since we have not gotten
a response,
we are giving you
a final courtesy call.
She's with the doctors,
probably.
-Yeah, yeah, sure, sure.
Yeah, yeah, sure. Probably.
But then again, maybe not.
Maybe something did happen.
People always say
don't assume the worst. Why?
Sometimes, the worst is exactly
what you should assume.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
It's getting good.
You know, the waitress
is gonna be back any second.
Tuna melts cook fast.
You just throw everything
under the heat lamp.
So I'm gonna ask you
one final time --
the truth.
-I'm telling you,
you got me confused --
-You're telling me --
-Yeah, I'm trying to.
-Stop the phony.
Stop the phony. Tick, tick.
-I don't know what to tell you.
-The truth! The truth!
That's it. Just the truth.
Tick, tick, tick.
-You think I'm --
I'm someone that I'm not.
-And why, may I ask,
would you think that I think
you're someone you're actually
not?
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick?
-What?
-Did you not just
fucking hear me right then?
-Yeah, I did.
-Well, then would you do me
a favor and would you please
stop saying "what?"
when it's absolutely crystal
fucking clear what I just said?
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
Okay. You know what?
You should prepare yourself,
mindset-wise.
That way, it won't be
such a shock when it happens.
Assume the worst is what I mean.
-Just tell me what
you want me to say.
Just tell me.
- Oh, my God.
You're not changing
your tactics.
Not even a little.
It's fucking mental.
You're awesome, buddy!
-I'm not who you think I am!
-I never even told you
who I think you are!
So how could you know
you're not who I think you are?!
Tick, tick, tick, tick!
-I'll say whatever you want.
-Okay. You know what?
Time's up.
You really just unequivocally
fucked up right now.
You fucked up --
Hey.
-Run.
-Okay. Okay!
-It's --
It's me.
-I'm exactly who you think
I am.
-It's you?
It's you.
It's fucking you!
It's you! Fucking you!
It's you! It's you!
It's you! It's you! You!
James.
You did this.
-You said that thing
about slipping me
a block of cheddar cheese
under the table?
Was that sarcasm?
Were being rude?
Or were you being nice?
I was being a dick.
-911, what's your emergency?
-There's a man. He's --
He's -- He's killing people.
He shot people.
-Sir, where are you located?
-Well, it's a --
It's a -- it's a diner.
Roadhouse Diner.
-I heard you, sir.
Be patient.
We will get to you.
-James!
-James.
Better to reign in hell,
wouldn't you agree?
-James!
James!
- James!
Great night.
Great fucking night.
I've been watching
for a while now, James.
Watching and waiting.
You, the wife,
the little boy.
I need you to wake up now.
Time for you
to wake up, asshole!
Gotta wake...up!
-You know who I am.
You know where I've been.
Pick up the phone, James!
I know you'll loop back around.
I heard the phone ringing.
Did you pick up?
What, what are you,
ghosting me?!
What are you, Dr. Ross,
my psychiatrist?
-Alright, Well, I'm gonna
finish the bookkeeper story.
And this next part,
I just know you're gonna love.
'Cause it directly
concerns you.
So everything goes
according to plan.
Bookkeeper invites
the associate over.
Sullivan's guys
shoot him in the head.
Except for one
very minor hitch.
See?
Very minor hitch...
being that...
the bookkeeper's wife...
steps through the door.
...and witnesses the execution.
So one problem begets
additional problems, right?
And the bookkeeper's wife
begins to unravel.
She starts drinking.
She starts taking pills.
She starts telling the story
to anyone who will listen.
My wife, James.
She's become a liability.
And that's when I got a call
from James Levine.
-The eighth floor...
Labor & Delivery.
Room 829!
-As I was saying, your wife's
at Labor & Delivery
on the eighth floor,
room 829.
Now, I don't kill mothers,
as a rule,
unlike some people I know,
but I swear to God, James,
if you don't stop acting like
this funny little bitch,
I'll break my own rule
just this one time.
-Okay.
-For you.
-I'll do whatever you want.
Just tell me what you
want me to do and I'll do it.
-You'll get back in your car
right now,
and I promise,
we'll stay away from your wife.
-You,
your associates or whatever,
you stay the fuck away
from my family.
-You have my word.
-What happened to...your wife
and daughter?
-I got a call from James Levine,
and Levine is someone who...
fixes things, whatever it is.
and I know if I'm getting a call
from him out of the blue,
it is not a small thing.
He tells me
what I already know --
that my wife
has become a liability.
That Jacob Sullivan himself
needs me to get control
of my wife,
that she could be the string
that unravels it all.
-What happened?
-I tell Levine
I'll take care of it.
Knowing what sort of man Levine
is, I decide my only choice
is to get my family out
of Boston for good.
So I -- I leave the house,
quickly to get some supplies
for the road,
and when I come back...
Back then we had these --
these white rabbits as pets.
And they had babies,
so we had a good-sized litter,
and my daughter, she -- she
liked to play with the babies.
She was so cute.
She'd rub her little face
in their soft white fur.
When I come back...
the entire house
was up in flames.
It was glowing,
all glowing orange,
like a --
like a jack o' lantern.
My wife and daughter inside.
But it was the rabbits, James.
Do you remember?
Did you hear the rabbits
screaming?
Shrieking?
-I know I'm gonna die tonight.
I understand.
And you made a promise that
I know you're going to keep.
-And I keep my word.
-But I want you to know...
that I am...
David Chamberlain --
-You are so fucked
in the head, James!
You're so fucked in the head,
you actually believe
you're David Chamberlain!
- The thing about lung cancer.
They're dying, right?
-We're all dying.
-So this was always
the end for you, too.
-These fucking cops.
You know,
the Japanese say,
the more violent the death,
the higher the heaven you go.
Alright.
-Okay. Let's do this.
-Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
I need to know.
Why didn't you just kill me
the second you stepped
into my car?
Why let me breathe
another second?
-'Cause I wanted to hear you
say it out loud.
The words.
-What words?
-And I wanted to see
your face.
Your true face.
Your lizard face reawoke.
-What words?
I-I-I'll say it right now.
Sullivan, he told me...
Sullivan. He ordered the hit.
-I need you to know...
I never meant to kill
your little girl.
Your wife, when she saw my face,
she just went crazy.
She just jumped on me
and started clawing my face off,
and I pulled the trigger
three times.
And your d--
Your daughter...
-Just lying in the hallway.
-I was drinking myself to death
when God brought Maggie
into my life.
And I knew God was evening the
score when our firstborn died.
But still, every night,
I'd see their faces.
Your wife and your daughter.
I-I-I couldn't stop seeing her.
Then when God gave me
my little baby boy,
it was like he was giving me
a new life.
He was giving me back
your daughter's life.
He was -- He was giving me back
your daughter's life,
the life that I wrongly took.
I think you gave me
closure tonight.
I wish I could have done
the same for you.
I'll --
-David,
I've been calling and calling.
Please call me back.
Please say you're okay.
We had a little girl, David.
I'm holding her.
She's so beautiful.
She has your eyes.
I don't know who that was
on the phone earlier, but...
I know you're okay.
I just feel it.
I'm praying, David.
I'm praying God will help you
find your way back to us.
We're waiting for you.
Both of us.
-David Chamberlain.
I'm David Chamberlain.
David Chamberlain.
-I'm David Chamberlain.
-Help!
-Not responding.
He's not responding!
Stay right there!
Don't move!
-Put your hands up!